Josh Watson

Melbourne, Victoria | M: 0425 838 123 | E: joshjkwatson@gmail.com

GitHub: Joshua-Watson96 | LinkedIn:/in/josh-watson-65a22b267/

SUMMARY

I have always had a passion for coding and tech. It is an industry I have always wanted to get into but life took a different path after high school. The spark recently reignited this year and I am trying to improve my knowledge of Software Engineering and make a career out of it and see where it takes me. I am hard working and always up to a challenge. I have leadership experience, great communication skills and love working in a team environment.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

• Front-end: JavaScript, CSS, HTML

• Back-end: Node.js, Express, MySQL, NoSQL, MongoDB

PROJECTS

TravelWise(Co-Developer) | https://joshua-watson96.github.io/Travel-Wise/index.html

WORK EXPERIENCE

Manager | Let Danny Do It

Melbourne, Victoria | AUG 2017 - PRESENT

• Let Danny Do It is a removals and transport company. I managed and at times ran the company. I had to manage a team of 8-10 on a day-to-day basis and set up the logistics and logistical software(vWork) for the company.

Laborer | Who Group

Melbourne, Victoria | Jan 2016 - Aug 2017

• At Who Group, I did various tasks on a construction site.

ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE

Volunteer | VMCH

Melbourne, Victoria | March 2017 - Present

• I volunteer for VillaMaria Catholic Homes. I help sort clothes for the op-shops the organization ran, and help with assortment of events.

EDUCATION

Certificate: Full Stack Web Development | Feb 2023 - Aug 2023 | Monash University |
Melbourne, Victoria